in this tutorial we'll be going over how
在本教程中，我们将介绍如何
you can divide your artwork up into
你可以把你的作品分成
individual Carousel slides and then
单独的旋转木马幻灯片，然后
export them as individual PNG or jpeg
将它们作为单独的PNG或jpeg导出
images using inkscape so I'll go ahead
使用Inkscape的图像，因此我将继续
and get started here in inkscape the
从这里开始使用Inkscape
example we'll be working with for this
我们将在此使用的示例
demonstration is the Instagram Carousel
演示是Instagram旋转木马
slide which they recommend a size of
他们推荐的幻灯片大小为
1080 by 1350 so what I'm going to do is
1080年到1350年，所以我要做的是
grab the rectangle tool and I'm going to
抓起矩形工具，我要
click and drag to draw a rectangle and I
单击并拖动以绘制一个矩形，然后我
want to make this to be 1080 width by
我想把这个做成1080宽乘以
1350 height so I will grab my selection
1350米，所以我会拿起我的选择
tool I'll come up here to where the
工具，我会来到这里，在那里
width and height inputs are and I'll
宽度和高度输入是，我将
change the width to well first of all
首先将宽度更改为Well
make sure you're working with pixels
确保您使用的是像素
here and then make sure this lock icon
在这里，然后确保这个锁图标
is turned off and I will make this a
已关闭，我将把它设置为
width of 1080.
宽度为1080。
and then I will make this a height of
然后我会把它变成一个高度的
1350.
1350。
and now we have the size this represents
现在我们有了它代表的大小
one slide on the carousel so if you want
旋转木马上的一张幻灯片，所以如果你想
to have three or four slides we're going
我们要做三四张幻灯片
to have to create three or four copies
必须创建三到四个副本
of this and stack them next to each
并将它们堆叠在每个
other so let me first change the
其他的，所以让我先改变一下
documents so that it's the size of this
文件，所以它的大小是这个
rectangle here so with the rectangle
这里是矩形，所以这个矩形
selected I'm just going to press Ctrl
已选中，我只需按Ctrl键
shift r on the keyboard or if you're
在键盘上按下Shift r键，或者如果您正在
using Mac it would be command shift R
使用Mac时，它将是命令Shift R
and it's going to resize the document to
它会将文档大小调整为
the selection as you can see there and
你可以在那里看到的选择和
now we want to get rid of that border
现在我们想要摆脱这一边界
and the shadow around the border so let
和边界周围的阴影让我们
me go to document properties I'll go to
我转到文档属性，我将转到
file
文件
document properties
文档属性
and where it says border let's first
在它说边界的地方，让我们首先
turn off the Border shadow
关闭边界阴影
and then we will turn off the Border
然后我们将关闭边境
altogether
总而言之
and then we can close out of this menu
然后我们就可以关闭这个菜单了
so we now have a single document for a
因此，我们现在只有一个文档，用于
single tile so what we have to do is
一块瓷砖，所以我们要做的是
create three or four duplicate copies of
创建三个或四个副本
this for the for this demonstration I
这是用于此演示的
will create three slides if you want to
如果您愿意，我将创建三张幻灯片
create more you can go ahead and do that
创造更多，你可以继续这样做
first I'm going to turn on snapping up
首先，我要打开抢购
here in this top right corner and then
在这个右上角，然后
I'm going to snap this rectangle to the
我要把这个矩形按到
right hand side of the page there like
页面的右手边就像
that and then I will grab the documents
然后我就去拿文件
tool down here
工具在这里
I will snap to the bottom right corner
我将捕捉到右下角
then click and drag and then snap to the
然后单击并拖动，然后捕捉到
top left corner to draw the second page
左上角绘制第二页
and if I move this over we now have a
如果我把这个移过去，我们现在就有一个
second document there now it looks like
那里的第二个文档现在看起来像
one continuous document but these are
一个连续的文档，但这些是
two separate two separate documents here
这里有两个不同的文档
we have page one and then page two
我们有第一页，然后是第二页
so now I'm going to create my third
所以现在我要创造我的第三个
slide I'm going to snap this over here
幻灯片我要把这张照片拍下来
to the right hand side
右手边
and I will grab my documents tool again
我会再次拿起我的文档工具
snap to the bottom right corner
捕捉到右下角
click and drag
单击并拖动
there we go there's page three so let me
好了，第三页了，让我来吧
grab this and move this out of the way
拿着这个，把这个移开
I'm just going to work with three slides
我只需要用三张幻灯片来工作
for this demonstration so I'm going to
对于这个演示，所以我要
delete this rectangle now if you want
如果需要，请立即删除此矩形
four or five slides you'll just have to
四五张幻灯片，你只需要
repeat that process a few more times but
重复这个过程几次，但是
we now have the template that we can use
现在我们有了可以使用的模板
to design our independent slides and I'm
设计我们的独立幻灯片，而我
gonna for this demonstration I'm gonna
为了这次演示，我要
bring in an image that I've downloaded
带上我下载的一张图片
from a stock photo site let me just open
从一个库存照片网站让我打开
this up I have this on my other screen
在我的另一个屏幕上有这个
over here I'm going to click and drag
在这里，我要点击并拖动
the image onto my canvas like that
像这样把图像放到我的画布上
okay so now I have imported my artwork
好了，现在我已经导入了我的艺术品
onto the canvas the problem that we have
把我们所面临的问题放在画布上
now is that you can't see exactly where
现在的问题是，你看不到确切的位置
the artwork lines up with the canvas so
这幅画与画布对齐，所以
we're going to re-enable borders so that
我们将重新启用边界，以便
we can see that let me place this on top
我们可以看到，让我把这个放在上面
of the top of the document like that and
像这样放在文档的顶部
then I will open up the document
那我就把文件打开
properties menu again file document
属性菜单再次文件文档
properties
属性
and now
而现在
I'm going to turn the Border back on
我要重新打开边界
I'm going to make it so that the border
我要做的就是让边界
is always on top I'm going to tick that
总是在最上面，我要勾选这个
box and now you will see the border on
框中，现在您将看到边框
top of your artwork and I'm going to
你的艺术作品的顶端，我要
leave show shadow turned off that's not
离开显示阴影已关闭这不是
necessary and depending on the
必要的，并且取决于
composition of your image you may want
您可能需要的图像构图
to change the color of your border if
要更改边框的颜色，请执行以下操作
you notice here my border is kind of
你注意到了吗，我的边界有点
blending in with the image it doesn't
与它所不具备的形象融为一体
stand out very well so I'm going to make
脱颖而出，所以我要做
this border white so I'm going to change
这个边框是白色的，所以我要换掉
the Border color up here
这里的边框颜色
then I'm going to make this white
然后我要把这个涂成白色
and you can see you can see that border
你可以看到你可以看到那个边框
much better now
现在好多了
and if you want to bring down the
如果你想把
opacity of it so it isn't so sharp you
它不透明，所以它不会那么锋利
could bring this down a little bit and
可以把这一点降下来，
now it gives you a better idea of what
现在，它让您更好地了解
the continuous image will look like
连续的图像将如下所示
because the Border isn't so prominent
因为边界并不是那么突出
there so let me close out of that now
好了，现在让我结束这一切吧
and we now have our document set up with
我们现在已经设置了我们的文档
three different Carousel slides that we
三个不同的旋转木马幻灯片，我们
can add our contents to so I'm going to
可以将我们的内容添加到，所以我要
resize my image to fit this better I'm
调整我的形象以更好地适应这一点
going to turn off snapping now we don't
现在我们不能关闭快照
need that anymore
再也不需要它了
and I'm going to hold Ctrl while I'm
我要按住Ctrl键
scaling and I'm going to place my
我要把我的
artwork right about where I want the
关于我想要的地方的艺术品
three slides to be so in this first
在第一个幻灯片中将有三张幻灯片
slide I want the subject to be in here
幻灯片我想把主题放在这里
and then the last two slides I can let
然后最后两张幻灯片我可以让
it be the rest of the image like that
图像的其余部分都是这样的
and what you could do now is you can go
你现在可以做的是你可以走了
through here and add some contents so I
通过这里并添加一些内容，所以我
think for this demonstration I'll just
考虑到这个演示，我只想
add some simple little dummy text and
添加一些简单的虚拟文本，然后
then we'll take it from there
那我们就从那里开始吧
okay so I have some sample text in there
好的，我在里面有一些样本文本
if you want to make sure that your
如果您想确保您的
elements that your design elements are
您的设计元素是
aligning perfectly with each individual
完美地与每个个体保持一致
slide of the carousel just open up your
旋转木马的滑梯只需打开你的
aligned distribute menu by going to
对齐分发菜单，方法是转到
object and selecting align and
对象，然后选择对齐和
distribute down here at the bottom of
在这里向下分布在底部
the list
这份名单
and then set the relative to set this to
然后将Relative设置为
page and now whichever page you have the
页面，现在您有哪个页面
design element placed over you can
放置在上面的设计元素可以
Center and align it based on that
在此基础上居中对齐
particular page there so I'll make a
这里有特定的页面，所以我会做一个
duplicate of that by pressing Ctrl D and
通过按Ctrl D和复制该命令
I'll move this over here
我把这个搬到这里来
and then I will Center this up on this
然后我会把这个放在这里
page as well
页面也是如此
okay so let's say that this is the
好的，让我们假设这是
design I want to export these are the
我想要输出的设计这些是
three slides I want to work with here
我想在这里使用的三张幻灯片
to do this we're going to create
要做到这一点，我们将创建
separate images of each tile here using
此处每个瓷砖的单独图像使用
the batch export feature so let's go up
批量导出功能，因此让我们继续
to where it says file and go to export
到它所说的文件位置，然后转到出口
and then over here in the export menu
然后在这里的导出菜单中
we're going to choose batch export
我们将选择批量导出
because we want to export all three of
因为我们想要将所有三个
these slides at once
一次播放这些幻灯片
and we're going to choose pages over
我们会选择书页而不是
here and if you notice over here this is
这里，如果你注意到这里，这是
a preview of what's going to get
预览将会得到什么
exported we have page one page two and
出口我们有第一页和第二页
Page Three now if yours is not in order
如果你的书不符合要求，现在就翻第三页
don't worry sometimes it just indexes
不要担心，有时它只是索引而已
them here in the wrong order but they
它们在这里的顺序是错误的，但它们
will be exported with the proper name
将使用正确的名称导出
and the and in the proper order so uh
并按正确的顺序排列，所以呢
this this title page one page two page
这是标题页一页两页
three down here you can choose like a
这里有三个，你可以像这样选择
prefix for the name
名称的前缀
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
我要做的是我要
click this little folder icon over here
点击这里的这个小文件夹图标
to choose where I would like to export
选择我想要出口的位置
these designs
这些设计
so what you can do here is change the
因此，您在这里可以做的是更改
name of the files that will be exported
要导出的文件的名称
the default here as you can see is
如您所见，此处的默认设置为
bitmap.png if I leave the default here
Bitmap.png，如果我在此处保留默认设置
as it is the files are going to be saved
如果是这样，文件将被保存
with the names bitmap Dash page1.png and
名称为Bitmap Dash page1.png和
then page2.png and so on and so forth
然后是page2.png等等
I'm just going to leave that as it is
我只想让它保持原样
down here you can choose your file type
在这里您可以选择您的文件类型
if you'd like the default is PNG but if
如果您希望默认设置为PNG，但如果
you want to export as JPEG or Tiff or
您想要导出为JPEG或Tiff或
webp there you go there that option is
WebP你去那里，那个选项是
and I'm going to click save and what
我会点击保存然后什么
I'll do here is I will just put up on
我在这里要做的就是忍受
the screen here the result of exporting
这里的屏幕是输出的结果
these three documents as individual
这三份文件作为个人
Carousel slides and you can now upload
旋转幻灯片，您现在可以上传
these to Instagram or wherever else to
这些到Instagram或其他任何地方
have three separate images that make one
有三个独立的图像，构成一个
continuous image so that's how you can
连续图像，这就是您可以的方式
divide your artwork up into individual
将您的艺术作品分成单独的作品
Carousel slides using inkscape if you
如果您使用inkscape旋转幻灯片
found this lesson useful then consider
发现这堂课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的水墨风景大师班
it's a collection of over 60 videos
它包含60多个视频
where I go over all of the tools and
我会检查所有工具，
features in inkscape and I explain what
水墨景观中的特征，我解释了什么
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示它们如何工作
kind of like how I did in this video we
有点像我在这个视频中所做的那样，
even have a private Community where you
甚至有一个私人社区，您可以在其中
can ask questions and get help for me
可以为我提问并寻求帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何时候您想要的，最重要的是，有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
只需支付每月会员费
17 one time and you're in for Life I'll
17一次，你就会终生难忘我会
have some information about that down
有一些相关信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想检查一下，请在下面作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看
foreign
外国
[Music]
[音乐]